Curto, Ernest; Papers apap238
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Bills, 1956-1964; Undated; 2; 2.6 cubic ft.
  - Bill Files, 1958-1964; Undated; 2.2
    - INT. 2666- Court of Claims, Jurisdiction of Janiak Compensation Claim, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 147)
    - INT. 2667- Real Property, Licensing of Nonresident Real Estate Brokers and Salesmen, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 148)
    - INT. 2681- General City, Annexation of Territory, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 149)
    - INT. 3138- General City. Meeting Rooms for Regular Veterans Association, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 150)
    - INT. 3139- Payments to Schools in Lieu of Taxes, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 151)
    - INT. 3193- Niagara Falls Arterial Highways, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 152)
    - INT. 3388- Real Property Tax, Publication of Exempt Properties List, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 153)
    - INT. 3892- Niagara Falls Arterial Highways, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 154)
    - INT. 4375- General Municipal, Urban Renewal Programs, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 155)
    - INT. 4376- Condemnation, Utilization of Taken Property, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 156)
    - INT. 4482- Education, Liability of Parents for Destruction of School Property, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 157)
    - INT. 4483- Condemnation, Damages, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 158)
    - INT. 4723- Conservation, Fish Management, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 159)
    - INT. 4785- Lewiston, Sale of Land for Streets, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 160)
    - INT. 4786- Real Property Tax, School Taxes, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 161)
    - INT. 4823- Tax, Compensation of Surrogates for Administration of Estate Taxes, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 162)
    - INT. 4951- Real Property Tax, State Aid to Districts, Public Utilities, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 163)
    - INT. 4962- Real Property Tax, State Aid to Districts, Power Authority, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 164)
    - INT. 4983- Real Property Tax, State Aid to Districts, Public Utilities, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 165)
    - Senate INT. 1913- General City, Annexation of Territory to Cities, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 166)
    - INT. 29- Interpleader Contract, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 1)
    - INT. 32- Business Corporation, Incorporating Civil Practice Provisions, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 2)
    - INT. 177- Workmen's Compensation, Disability Benefits Commutation, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 3)
    - INT. 178- Labor, Unemployment Insurance, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 4)
    - INT. 179- Workmen's Compensation, Hospitalization Benefits, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 5)
    - INT. 1376- Town of Lewiston, Sale of Land to Presbyterian Trustees, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 6)
    - INT. 1620- Banking, License Fees for Sales Finance Companies, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 7)
    - INT. 1621- Banking, Definition of Sales Finance Companies, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 8)
    - INT. 1622- Banking, Definition of Sales Finance Companies, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 9)
    - INT. 1623- Banking, Retail Installment Contracts, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 10)
    - INT. 1625- Personal Property, Trust Receipts and Mortgage Statements, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 11)
    - INT. 1626- Personal Property and Banking, Installment Sales, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 12)
    - INT. 1627- Personal Property, Protection for Buyers of Merchandise Certificates, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 13)
    - INT. 1641- Workmen's Compensation, Silicosis Disability, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 14)
    - INT. 1861- Education Death Benefit for Retired Teachers, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 15)
    - INT. 1862- Education, Physical Therapists, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 16)
    - INT. 1906- Labor, Maximum Hours for Firemen, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 17)
    - INT. 1951- General Municipal, Prohibition of Consolidation of Police and Fire Departments, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 18)
    - INT. 1992- Highway, Prequalification of Prospective Bidders, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 19)
    - INT. 1993- Court of Claims, Jurisdiction in Claims Against the State, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 20)
    - INT. 1994- Court of Claims, Jurisdiction to Render Declaratory Judgments, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 21)
    - INT. 2310- Family Court Act, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 22)
    - INT. 2313- Workmen's Compensation, Uninsured Employers' Fund, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 23)
    - INT. 2329- Multiple Residence, Elevator and Dumbwaiter Doors, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 24)
    - INT. 2330- Railroad, Requires Tops, Windshields, and Wipers for Employee Cars, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 25)
    - INT. 2331- Retirement, Social Security, and Education, Final Average Salary, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 26)
    - INT. 2332- Condemnation, Damages, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 27)
    - INT. 2719- Real Property Tax, Conveyances of Real Property, Niagara County, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 28)
    - INT. 2797- General Business, Licensing and Regulation of Collection Agencies, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 29)
    - INT. 2858- Multiple Dwelling, Exit Signs, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 30)
    - INT. 3030- Real Property Tax, State Aid to Districts, Power Authority, 1961-1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 31)
    - INT. 3031- Real Property Tax, Publication of Exempt Properties List, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 32)
    - INT. 3349- General City, Contribution to City Employee[ Medical Benefits, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 33)
    - INT. 3350- Education, Teachers' Pensions, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 34)
    - INT. 3415- Banking, Refund of Personal Loan Fines, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 35)
    - INT. 3478- Penal, Strikebreakers, Regulations, 1962-1964; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 36)
    - INT. 3478- Penal, Strikebreakers, Regulations, 1962-1964; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 37)
    - INT. 3517- Judiciary, Compensation of Family Court Judges, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 38)
    - INT. 3623- Labor, Unintentional Errors in Unemployment Insurance, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 39)
    - INT. 3625- State Prison Guard Retirement, Age 50, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 40)
    - INT. 3647- Traffic and Vehicles, Stop Signs at Railroad Crossings, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 41)
    - INT. 3732- Court of Claims, Jurisdiction of Sondek Compensation Claim, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 42)
    - INT. 3839- Intervention of Attorney General in Cases of Public Interest, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 43)
    - INT. 3981- Penal, Admission of Children to Bowling Alleys, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 44)
    - INT. 3982- Finance, Public Housing Bonds, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 45)
    - INT. 3983- Private Housing Finance, Incorporation of Redevelopment Companies, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 46)
    - INT. 4269- Private Housing Finance, State Supervision of Limited Dividend Housing Companies, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 47)
    - INT. 4283- Private Housing Finance Law, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 48)
    - INT. 4418- Niagara Falls Arterial Highways, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 49)
    - INT. 4419- Niagara Falls Arterial Highways, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 50)
    - INT. 4502- General Municipal, Urban Renewal Projects in Smaller Communities, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 51)
    - INT. 4513- Agriculture and Markets, Sale of Meat with "Cod-Fat", 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 52)
    - INT. 4514- Real Property, Licensing of Nonresident Real Estate Brokers and Salesmen, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 53)
    - INT. 4535- Labor, State Manpower Council, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 54)
    - INT. 4668- Criminal Procedure Code, Bail Bond Premiums, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 55)
    - INT. 4805- Power of Cities to Contract Indebtedness for Slum Clearance, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 56)
    - INT. 4850- Private Housing Finance, Tax Abatement for Limited Dividend Projects, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 57)
    - INT. 4904- Constitutional Amendment, Municipal Indebtedness Exemption for Sewers, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 58)
    - INT. 4916- Private Housing Finance, Limited Profit Housing Company, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 59)
    - INT. 4917- Constitutional Amendment, Municipal Indebtedness, Urban Renewal Projects, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 60)
    - INT. 4955- Annexation, Wheatfield, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 61)
    - INT. 4956- Annexation, Town of Niagara, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 62)
    - INT. 4959- Banking, Premium Finance, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 63)
    - INT. 4993- Niagara Falls Fire Department Insurance Premium Tax, 1962; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 64)
    - INT. 5103- Payments to Schools in Lieu of Taxes, Power Authority, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 65)
    - INT. 50- Retirement, Social Security, and Education, Final Average Salary, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 66)
    - INT. 80- Labor, Strikebreakers, Regulations, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 67)
    - INT. 233- Public Lands, Power to Confirm Defective Grants, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 68)
    - INT. 233- Public Lands, Power to Confirm Defective Grants (Senate Version), 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 69)
    - INT. 234- Public Lands, Maps of Unappropriated State Lands, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 70)
    - INT. 234- Public Lands, Maps of Unappropriated State Lands (Senate Version), 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 71)
    - INT. 235- Public Lands and General City, Sale of Formerly Underwater Land, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 72)
    - INT. 353- Niagara Falls Fire Department Insurance Premium Tax, 1962-1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 73)
    - INT. 577- Constitutional Amendment, Municipal Indebtedness Exemption for Sewers, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 74)
    - INT. 1043- Personal Property, Retail Installment Forms, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 75)
    - INT. 1043- Personal Property, Retail Installment Forms (Amended Print), 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 76)
    - INT. 1044- Personal Property, Credit Service Charges, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 77)
    - INT. 1045- General Business, Collection Agencies, 1960; 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 78)
    - INT. 1045- General Business, Collection Agencies (Amended Print), 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 79)
    - INT. 1194- Labor, Unemployment Insurance, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 80)
    - INT. 1195- Non-occupational Disability Benefits Formula, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 81)
    - INT. 1196- State Prison Guard Optional Retirement, 1962-1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 82)
    - INT. 1441- General Municipal, Police and Fire Departments, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 83)
    - INT. 1653- Workmen's Compensation, Optometrists Selection, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 84)
    - INT. 1654- Executive, Administrative Proceedings Regulations, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 85)
    - INT. 1654- Executive, Administrative Proceedings Regulations (Amended Print), 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 86)
    - INT. 1770- Constitutional Amendment, Urban Renewal Programs, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 87)
    - INT. 1770- Constitutional Amendment, Urban Renewal Programs (Amended Print), 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 88)
    - INT. 1771- Multiple Residence, Egress to Stairs, 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 89)
    - INT. 1772- Public Housing, Temporary Tenants, 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 90)
    - INT. 1900- Public Lands, Notice of Sale or Lease, 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 91)
    - INT. 1900- Public Lands, Notice of Sale or Lease (Amended Print), 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 92)
    - INT. 1941- Insurance, Credit Insurance Limits, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 93)
    - INT. 1984- Non-occupational Disability Additional Benefits, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 94)
    - INT. 1985- Personal Property, Definition of Note holders, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 95)
    - INT. 2235- Public Lands, Public Notice of Sale or Lease, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 96)
    - INT. 2343- John Daddario Claim, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 97)
    - INT. 2343- John Daddario Claim Map, 1960 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 98)
    - INT. 2430- Civil Practice Law and Rules, Authentication of Conveyances, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 99)
    - INT. 2430- Civil Practice Law and Rules, Authentication of Conveyances (Amended Print), 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 100)
    - INT. 3378- Judiciary, Expenses of Court of Claims Judges, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 101)
    - INT. 3379- Education, State Aid Apportionment, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 102)
    - INT. 3380- Education, Retired Teachers Additional Pensions, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 103)
    - INT. 3381- Civil Practice Law and Rules, Confidentiality, Pharmacists, 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 104)
    - INT. 3481- Multiple Dwelling, Water Closet Regulations, 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 105)
    - INT. 3482- Public Service, Railroad Express Employees, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 106)
    - INT. 3687- Civil Service, Strikes by Public Employees, 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 107)
    - INT. 3702- Education, Teacher Termination Notices, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 108)
    - INT. 3749- Education, State Teachers Retirement Loans, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 109)
    - INT. 3750- William J. McDougall Et. Al. Claims, 1962-1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 110)
    - INT. 3892- County, Payments in Lieu of Taxes to Municipalities, 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 111)
    - INT. 3919- State Finance, Urban Renewal Programs, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 112)
    - INT. 3949- Mutual Nonprofit Dormitory Housing, 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 113)
    - INT. 3961- Civil Practice and Law, Proof of Service, 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 114)
    - INT. 3961- Civil Practice and Law, Proof of Service (Amended Print), 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 115)
    - INT. 3962- Civil Practice, Proof of Facts, 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 116)
    - INT. 3963- Real Property Actions, Infants Realty, 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 117)
    - INT. 3964- Real Property Actions, Tenants Rights, 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 118)
    - INT. 4033- Niagara County, Lewiston Town Lands, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 119)
    - INT. 4091- Court of Claims, Realty Condemnation Awards, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 120)
    - INT. 4123- General Municipal, Urban Renewal Agencies, 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 121)
    - INT. 4217- Penal, Admission of Children to Bowling Alleys, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 122)
    - INT. 4582- Public Lands, Underwater Land Grants, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 123)
    - INT. 4641- Civil Practice Law and Rules, Protection Order Motions, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 124)
    - INT. 4642- Multiple Dwelling, Conversion Regulations, 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 125)
    - INT. 4643- Lien, Contractors' Lien Waivers, 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 126)
    - INT. 4645- Dormitory Authority, Condemnation Power, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 127)
    - INT. 4709- General Municipal, Realty Condemnation Offers, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 128)
    - INT. 4711- General Municipal, Urban Renewal Plans, 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 129)
    - INT. 4711- General Municipal, Urban Renewal Plans (Amended Print), 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 130)
    - INT. 4712- Urban Renewal, Public Utility Systems, 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 131)
    - INT. 4714- Public Housing, Notice of Action, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 132)
    - INT. 4796- Niagara Falls, State Aid Funds, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 133)
    - INT. 4797- Niagara Falls Arterial Highways, 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 134)
    - INT. 4847- Local Finance, Bond Anticipation Notes, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 135)
    - INT. 4848- Real Property Tax, Tax Abatement for Slum Clearance, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 136)
    - INT. 4942- Niagara Falls, Public Market Lands, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 137)
    - INT. 5014- Family Court, Niagara County Judge, 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 138)
    - INT. 5115- Private Housing Finance, Community Development Corporations, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 139)
    - INT. 5143- Payments in Lieu of Taxes, Power Authority, 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 140)
    - INT. 5191- Payments to Schools in Lieu of Taxes, Power Authority, 1963; Undated (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 141)
    - Senate INT. 682- Election, Opening and Closing of Polls, 1963 (Box 12 (2-Bills), Folder 142)
    - Assembly Bill Calendar, 1964 March 04 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 1)
    - INT. 2- Reapportionment, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 2)
    - INT. 4- Reapportionment, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 3)
    - INT. 5- Election, Voting by Armed Forces, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 4)
    - INT. 232- Retirement, Social Security, and Education, Final Average Salary, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 5)
    - INT. 1148- Code of Criminal Procedure, Designation of Policemen as Peace Officers, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 6)
    - INT. 1179- Niagara Falls Fire Department Insurance Premium Tax, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 7)
    - INT. 1180- Workmen's Compensation, Hospitalization Benefits, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 8)
    - INT. 1181- Workmen's Compensation, Computation of Disability Benefits, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 9)
    - INT. 1182- Labor, Unemployment Insurance, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 10)
    - INT. 1282- General Municipal, Prohibition of Consolidation of Fire and Police Departments, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 11)
    - INT. 1554- Public Lands, Public Notice of Sale or Lease, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 12)
    - INT. 1734- Executive, Building Code Council Board of Review Members, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 13)
    - INT. 1772- Education, Apportionment for Capital Outlays, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 14)
    - INT. 1842- Town of Lewiston, Sale of Land to Presbyterian Trustees, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 15)
    - INT. 1863- Multiple Dwelling, Exhaust Ducts in Fireproof Vestibules, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 16)
    - INT. 1866- Multiple Residence, Review Board, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 17)
    - INT. 1872- Public Housing, Income Limits, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 18)
    - INT. 2106- Personal Property, Refinancing of Retail Installment Contracts, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 19)
    - INT. 2107- Banking, Small Loans Made Outside the State, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 20)
    - INT. 2108- Banking, Personal Property Purchases By Banks, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 21)
    - INT. 2163- General Business, Trading Stamp Company Regulation, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 22)
    - INT. 2269- General Municipal, Duration of Term for Members of Urban Renewal Agencies, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 23)
    - INT. 2270- Real Property Tax, Tax Abatement for Property Improvements, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 24)
    - INT. 2290- Education, Teachers' Pensions, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 25)
    - INT. 2315- Education, Termination of Probationary Teachers, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 26)
    - INT. 2361- Real Property Action, Publication of Sale Notices, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 27)
    - INT. 2362- Lien, Down Payment Protection, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 28)
    - INT. 2531- Real Property Tax, Tax Exemption of Housing Facilities, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 29)
    - INT. 2532- Labor, Strikebreakers, Regulations, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 30)
    - INT. 2618- Court of Claims, Jurisdiction of Criswell Settlement, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 31)
    - INT. 2858- Real Property, Broker Licensing, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 32)
    - INT. 3075- Labor, Maximum Hours for Firemen, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 33)
    - INT. 3174- Penal, Admission of Children to Bowling Alleys, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 34)
    - INT. 3301- General Municipal, Urban Renewal Housing Relocation Planning, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 35)
    - INT. 3315- General Municipal, Establishment of the Niagara Falls Urban Renewal Agency, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 36)
    - INT. 3802- Banking, Real Estate Loans, 1963-1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 37)
    - INT. 3803- Education, Budget Filing Repeal, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 38)
    - INT. 4181- Civil Practice, Disposition of Property By Court, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 39)
    - INT. 4182- Civil Practice, Administration of Oaths and Affirmations, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 40)
    - INT. 4183- Civil Practice, Proof of Application for Judgment by Default, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 41)
    - INT. 4231- Education, Teachers' Pensions, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 42)
    - INT. 4319- Public Service, Duty to Protect Railroad Employees, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 43)
    - INT. 4657- Real Property Tax, Village Taxes, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 44)
    - INT. 4658- Niagara Falls, Sale of Land for Public Market, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 45)
    - INT. 4659- Annexation, Town of Niagara, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 46)
    - INT. 4811- Condemnation, Prorata of Taxes and Utilities, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 47)
    - INT. 4946- Private Housing Finance, Limited Profit Housing, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 48)
    - INT. 4947- Multiple Dwelling, Installation of Gas Meters, 1964; Undated (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 49)
    - INT. 5202- Labor, Unintentional Errors in Unemployment Insurance, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 50)
    - INT. 5323- Real Property Tax, State Aid for Tax Losses, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 51)
    - INT. 5338- Uniform City Court Act, Jurors, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 52)
    - Second Extraordinary Session INT. 15- State Accelerated Highway Fund, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 53)
    - Second Extraordinary Session INT. 16- State University Building Trust Account, 1964 (Box 13 (2-Bills), Folder 54)
    - Senate INT. 1- Reapportionment, 1964 (Box 14 (2-Bills), Folder 1)
    - Senate INT. 2- Reapportionment, 1964 (Box 14 (2-Bills), Folder 2)
    - Senate INT. 3- Reapportionment, 1964 (Box 14 (2-Bills), Folder 3)
- Legislative Correspondence, 1944; 1946-1965; Undated; 3; 4.0 cubic ft.
  Constituent subseries is arranged alphabetically by geographic location of the sender.
  General subseries is arranged chronologically by year.
  This series, divided into two subseries, contains incoming and outgoing correspondence related to the legislative activities of Assemblyman Ernest Curto. Also in this series are enclosures that were included with the original correspondence including copies of legislation, resolutions, newspaper clippings, brochures, reports, and other materials.
  The constituent correspondence subseries is in the original order that Curto and his staff kept the files in. For this subseries, they chose to organize it by geographical location of the sender, and these locations corresponded to places in Curto’s Assembly District.